  <!--
  INTRODUCTION
  -->

  <chapter id="intro">
    <title>Introdution</title>

    <para>
      The Caroshi is an application framework focused on development
      of HTML frontends in php. It doesn't depend on other libraries and can
      be used freely under the terms of the Lesser GNU Public License..
    </para>
      
    <para>
      Like most frameworks this one takes repetitive work off you and makes
      you feel like you were in Hollywood
      (&quot;Don't call us, we call you.&quot;), which is also know under
      the term <emphasis>event driven</emphasis>: You configure the
      behaviour of your application at startup and wait for events that
      come in and result into function calls to your program.
    </para>

    <para>
      Repetitively needed code like URL, SQL and HTML generation is hidden
      under some layers of objects combined by a GUI facade, reducing the
      number of classes that need to be known most of the time to 2.
    </para>

    <para>
      This manual is completely rewritten into a tutorial. If you want
      to find out about more features of the library, please refer to
      the API reference available online and with the package.
    </para>

    <sect1>
      <title>Release notes</title>
      <sect2>
        <title>0.1.0</title>
	<para>
          admin_panel is not backward-compatible. The directory structure
	  was cleaned up as well as many classes.
	</para>
      </sect2>
    </sect1>

    <sect1>
      <title>Contributors</title>

      <para>
        This software was influenced by the work and ideas of many people.
        Some of them are listed here in alphabetical order:
      </para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem><para>Andreas Ferber</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Garvin Gripp</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Michael Hinz-Renault</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Henry Jobst &lt;henry@jobst-berlin.de&gt;</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Sascha Krause &lt;sk@devcon.net&gt;</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Tim Mattison &lt;bdonor@cloud9.net&gt;</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Winfried Motzkus</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Bernhard Pietsch &lt;bp@devcon.net&gt;</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Christian Rish&oslash;j &lt;chrris@mail.dk&gt;</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Christine Sch&ouml;nfeld</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Friedhelm Sch&ouml;nfeld</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>Carlheinz Sockel &lt;chs@devcon.net&gt;</para></listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </sect1>
  </chapter>
